{
    "subject": "resource/Hod_Stuart",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/Ontario",
    "human_readable": "Hod Stuart died in Ontario.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8653130531311035,
            "question": "Where did Hod Stuart die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8607557415962219,
            "question": "Was Hod Stuart born in Ontario?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7318554520606995,
            "question": "Did Hod Stuart live in Ontario for his whole life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5436046719551086,
            "question": "Were there any notable events related to Hod Stuart's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41140639781951904,
            "question": "What was Hod Stuart known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3111983835697174,
            "question": "What is known about Hod Stuart's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27161574363708496,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Hod Stuart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2436705231666565,
            "question": "What other information do you have about Hod Stuart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2197185754776001,
            "question": "Is there any information about Hod Stuart's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17728272080421448,
            "question": "Are there any records of Hod Stuart's family?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hod Stuart died in Ontario.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6583_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information about Hod Stuart's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6583_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other information do you have about Hod Stuart?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6583_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Hod Stuart?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6583_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6583_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6583_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6583_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6583_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6583_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6583_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6583_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6583_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6583_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6583_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to the documents, Hod Stuart died in a diving incident in Bay of Quinte, Ontario on June 23, 1907 (document 1)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Hod Stuart died in a diving incident at the Bay of Quinte, which is located in Ontario. Therefore, the statement \"Hod Stuart died in Ontario\" is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}